Even the billions of heartbeats in the world
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
are nothing to you but insignificant
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Whether we’re trapped in the past or lamenting over the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
predetermination does not allow even the slightest mistake
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The infinite dreams and futures before us
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are but vain privileges allowed to us
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finitude is what both clock hands show
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
toward a cruel destiny and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
So now I cross worldlines every second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
because I want to protect that smile of yours
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And so, a time loop without sadness will once again
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
engulf me, the lone observer
I'm so hungry.
You're going to—
ComiMa again, right?
Yeah.
Will you be back by this time tomorrow?
I think so.
I know! Kurisu, you come too!
I don't really like crowded places.
It shouldn't be that crowded on the second day.
You should come too, Okarin...
Okabe, come with me!
What's with you?
Ever since you got back, you've been looking down.
Can't you tell Mayuri is trying to cheer you up?
I can tell.
But,
I can't stay calm!
Tomorrow is the day!
Even if she's safe today, tomorrow...
How many times have I talked to you about this?
Okabe?
There's something I want to tell you.
Endless
Apoptosis
Mayuri is going to die tomorrow?!
Most likely, yes.
At first, it was the night of the 13th.
But each time I undid a D-Mail, it happened one day later.
I'll have to go with her to ComiMa tomorrow.
Do you have a way to save her?
I'm going to wait for her to die.
You can't...
I need to know the precise deadline in this worldline.
Then, I can time leap back again.
There's no other way.
The next one to undo
is that Kiryu Moeka person's, right?
That's right.
I know what she sent.
She sent a message
telling herself not to buy a new cell phone.
This time, I need to send it from her phone.
You go find her...
I'll go with Mayuri to ComiMa.
You'll...
If all goes well,
I can protect Mayuri before she—
Don't you understand?
If I can't find Moeka, you'll—
I'll contact you right away.
And you can tell me anything, all right?
No matter what,
no matter when, come talk to me.
Yeah. You're still...
Don't forget.
No matter what worldline you're in, you aren't alone.
I'm here!
Assistant
From: Assistant
Now in Ariake
I'm in Ariake now.
Too many people here...
Way more than I expected.
Save me!
No response from Moeka, but I found her workplace.
I'll check it out.
Got it.
Take it easy.
Kiryu Moeka?
Oh yeah, that girl worked here two or three days and quit. That was her name.
Her address?
Yeah, I have it, but who are you?
Heights White
Kiryu Moeka
Roger.
Hey.
Kiryu Moeka...
She killed herself?
Are you sure?
Yes.
When?
Last night.
The body was taken to Chiyoda Hospital 3.
She doesn't seem to have any relatives.
No way.
Are you all right?
Suicide?
Why?
Did her companions kill her
before she could kill Mayuri?
But...
the reason doesn't matter!
At this rate, Mayuri will...
A time leap...
I need to time leap to before Moeka dies!
Hello?
Oka... Okabe!
She's...
Mayuri... Mayuri...
The deadline is 7:52 PM.
I'm sorry.
Okabe!
Did you eat this?
Look at the label!
It says "Makise" right here!
Are you listening?
Don't forget.
You aren't alone.
That's right.
You're right, Kurisu.
What did you just say?
Do you know a girl named Kiryu Moeka?
Who's that?
I just did a time leap.
What do you mean?
Heights White
FB...
Answer me...
Please...
FB...
Why?
Why won't you message me?
Please! Answer me!
FB...
Kiryu Moeka.
I did what you wanted, so why?
It's me, Okabe!
Give me your orders, FB!
Can't you hear me?!
FB...
N-No! No! No! Stop it!
I'll never...
forgive...
her!
G-Give it back.
Give it back!
Give it back!!
Okabe Rintaro
This is Makise.
Did you get the phone?
I stole it.
Prepare the D-Mail!
It's ready.
Give it back!
What's that sound?
Don't worry about it.
More importantly, what about Mayuri?
She's in Braun's TV Workshop.
The 42" is on.
Kurisu! Activate it!
Change your phone. It will sell out soon,
and you won't be able to get one.
Right!
Give it back!
This is it.
If I send this, Mayuri will...
Give it back! Give it back!
Give me back my phone!
What?
Nothing happened.
What's going on there?
Did you send it!
I did!
Is it working?
I saw the electricity.
What happened?
Reading Steiner didn't activate!
Reading Steiner didn't activate...
Why?
Give it back! Give it back!
Hey, what's going on?
Give it back! Give it back! Give it back!
It isn't working!
A D-Mail has different effects depending on who it was sent to.
Does this mean your message won't change her actions?
Then what do I do?
It didn't change.
She didn't change her cell phone!
What do you mean?
You confirmed it, right?
I changed my cell phone four days ago,
and I want to tell myself not to do it.
She sent another right after that!
But that means we don't know what was in that D-Mail!
It should be in her outbox!
I'll look...
Give it back!
What's wrong, Okabe?
Okabe?
I'll have to call you back!
Give it back!
Hey! What are you doing over there?
Okabe!
Give it back! Give it back!
Geez, what are they doing?
Hey...
Seriously! Couples these days...
How scary.
What do I have to do?
What do I have to do for you to give it back?
Do you remember sending a D-Mail?
A D— What?
Two weeks ago,
you should have received a strange message
from your future self.
Why?
Tell me what it said, and I'll give it back.
What's wrong? Can't you tell me?
Does it have something to do with the IBN 5100?
With the Rounders?
Am I right?!
Tell me! What did it say?
Don't you want your cell phone back?
I can't betray them.
Who?
That FB person?
I get my orders from FB.
FB is everything to me.
So that's your leader?
You can't betray FB?
It's great that you're so loyal.
But you know...
they don't give a damn about what happens to you.
They'll abandon you.
That's impossible.
They haven't contacted you, right?
You've been betrayed. Cut off!
No!
FB isn't like that!
FB saved me.
...in Cabinet Office...
You've been used!
Rounder Recruitment
Do you know why you can tell me these things?
FB is like a mother.
Subject: A Question
What kind of job is it?
Re: A Question
I have a type of time machine.
The message from the future is proof.
Another Question
Can I do it too?
Re: Another Question
Of course. We offer everyone
the job that best suits them.
They needed me.
I've never worked before.
I don't have skills or anything I'm good at.
It's okay.
Let's do our best together.
And I've seen it!
You...
You will kill yourself in this room four days from now.
You'll die here alone, still waiting to hear from FB!
Lies.
It's true.
You'll never hear from FB again.
You've been abandoned.
That's a lie...
How long has it been?
Well?
You've been waiting a while, right?
Don't you think that's strange?
You're going to die right here,
No...
in this dark, empty room.
No!
You killed Mayuri, and now you'll die!
Alone and betrayed like the
worthless piece of trash you are!
No!
You're going to kill yourself,
and nobody will save you!
Not even FB!
Sorry.
You said FB was like a mother.
Is FB a woman?
I think so.
You think?
We've never met.
I don't want to meet her.
If I did, she'd probably hate me.
From the look of it, I bet you've never spoken by phone either.
I'm amazed you did anything they ordered!
They gave me a place.
A place?
You're... a fool.
The retro-PC is
in Yanabayashi Shrine.
Recover it immediately.
Okabe?
Don't scare me like that!
You were worried about me?
I wasn't!
I'm sorry.
Well?
Then the one who stole the IBN 5100...
It was Moeka.
Where is she now?
Don't ask any more.
I'll undo the D-Mail as planned.
July 31st, around 11:00 AM, right?
Don't go to the shrine.
It's a trap. It isn't there!
It's on!
This time...
Why?
Well?
It didn't work!
The Kiryu Moeka from the past didn't believe the D-Mail?
She believed the first one, just in case?
You could try another message!
No...
I think there's only one person she'll follow.
If I send a message from that phone, she'll obey it,
no matter what it says!
Who is it?
I'm going to look for FB.
If you have any clues...
Even if you do, you won't tell me, huh?
Earlier, you were saying
that I killed someone. Is that in the future?
Yeah.
You'd do it if FB ordered you to, right?
I would. Absolutely.
Even if you knew you were being used?
You're going to die, abandoned and waiting...
Four days. August 15th.
The world itself has decided that you will die.
It's inevitable,
but I won't let it happen.
I'll fight the world,
and I will save Mayuri!
The coin locker...
in front of Daibiru.
The IBN 5100...
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
With my field of view restricted
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
I cannot escape the merciless control of the twelve
ansoku no asu wo negatta
While wishing for a tomorrow of repose
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
I headed for the sacred event horizon in my hand
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
Pledges are imprisoned, and false evidences are showing their outline
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
This world of life blindly lets the time pass by
habatake butterfly
Spread your wings
kiseki no butterfly
butterfly of miracles
anata he sasagu
I dedicate it to you
namida no butterfly
Oh butterfly of tears
mabushii butterfly
butterfly of radiance
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
everything will now be rewritten